[{"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b6de", "question": "What Winter Olympic sport event requires players to slide stones at houses?", "answer": "Curling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bbd4", "question": "What is the minimum Scoville rating for a Scotch Bonnet pepper?", "answer": "Around 150,000", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fd2d3172596a59cbdfbd397", "question": "What river flows into the world's largest waterfall?", "answer": "Zambezi River", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b737", "question": "London's Old Bailey is a what?", "answer": "Criminal court", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a320", "question": "In which 2003 film did Hugh Grant play the British Prime Minister?", "answer": "Love Actually", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b28c", "question": "What famous horse belonged to Napoleon?", "answer": "Marengo", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a40d", "question": "Devil's Island, once the world's most notorious penal colony, is located off the coast of what country?", "answer": "French Guiana", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c27d", "question": "What animals lives in a lodge?", "answer": "The beaver", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b93", "question": "Who is Becky Thatcher's boyfriend?", "answer": "Tom Sawyer", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b260", "question": "What did the US Federal Reserve system do a record seventeen consecutive times between 2004 and 2006?", "answer": "Raise interest rates", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5e94d2015ea27d7a1303aed7", "question": "In what US state is the Naismith Memorial Basketball Hall of Fame located?", "answer": "Massachusetts", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8ca", "question": "What San Francisco hill is home to a famous colony of wild parrots?", "answer": "Telegraph Hill", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5bfe00fcb668d7dfe168b5c7", "question": "When did Napoleon Bonaparte begin his reign as Emperor of the French?", "answer": "1804", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae13", "question": "In which decade was the Berlin Wall erected?", "answer": "1960s", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9b7", "question": "What name is given to twins who are joined together by some part of their anatomy?", "answer": "Siamese", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f9b", "question": "What's the appropriate stage name of musician Richard Melville Hall?", "answer": "Moby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d89", "question": "What original literary work was the movie \"Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory\" based on?", "answer": "Charlie and the Chocolate Factory", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8bf", "question": "What three-mile-wide New Brunswick island was FDR's summer home?", "answer": "Campobello", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "590499a3cf93664eb1048694", "question": "Who hosted the 2007 Brit Awards?", "answer": "Russell Brand", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a332", "question": "What was the name of Ross' pet monkey on the TV show \"Friends\"?", "answer": "Marcell", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5de655fff89b9ec3da2d335c", "question": "What auto company made the \"flathead\" V8 engine, which was the first affordable mass market V8?", "answer": "Ford", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399bc", "question": "How many episodes of \"The Beverly Hillbillies\" were made?", "answer": "274", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca50", "question": "Honeydew is a variety of what?", "answer": "Melon", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b2d", "question": "What was Mark Twain's real name?", "answer": "Samuel Clemens", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f16afdf7c52aae91cc07e4", "question": "The fillet of which fish is used to make \"rollmops\"?", "answer": "Herring", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a825", "question": "What large island lies about 300 miles due east of Mozambique?", "answer": "Madagascar", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133aeed", "question": "Which states did the US gain as a result of the Mexican-American War?", "answer": "New Mexico, California and Texas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601601a2fe83fe1f2a824c60", "question": "In what year were women first allowed to participate in the modern Olympic games?", "answer": "1900 -- in Paris", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea31ccff048f679a45aae5", "question": "How many eggs does a queen bee lay per day?", "answer": "2000", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd02", "question": "Who launched her signature fragrance, \"Moi\", in 1998?", "answer": "Miss Piggy", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fec86bcec223966ae8f8811", "question": "Who was the first female artist in history to have 4 consecutive singles from one album reach the Top 5 in the Billboard Hot 100?", "answer": "Cyndi Lauper's 1983 classic \"She's So Unusual\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "600f742fa9e54d890926f6f4", "question": "What country has competitive office chair racing?", "answer": "Japan", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133afd0", "question": "What was discovered in Sutter's Mill in California in 1848?", "answer": "Gold", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59f4730dcfb6472aeed499d4", "question": "How many Yahtzee \"bonus\" boxes are on a Yahtzee Score Card?", "answer": "3", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f0311338995", "question": "Who was married to Andrew Lloyd Webber when he composed \"The Phantom of the Opera\" for her voice?", "answer": "Sarah Brightman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5ce", "question": "Blue, Pinyon, and Steller's are species of what bird?", "answer": "Jay", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe69bc320565ad31a57c764", "question": "Who was the last king of Troy in Greek mythology?", "answer": "Priam", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be36", "question": "How many players are there in a standard water polo team?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133adc7", "question": "What was the name of the 1783 treaty that formally ended the American Revolutionary War?", "answer": "The Treaty of Paris", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c53c", "question": "What is the largest muscle in the human body?", "answer": "Gluteus Maximus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a2d2", "question": "Who played the role of C.K. Dexter-Haven in the 1956 film \"High Society\"?", "answer": "Bing Crosby", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a195", "question": "\"Love Bites\" was the only song to reach number one on the Billboard Hot 100 for which rock band?", "answer": "Def Leppard", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fb1bf51f497e33de805791a", "question": "What is the oldest active ballpark in Major League Baseball?", "answer": "Fenway Park", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0a9", "question": "What island nation was ruled by \"Papa Doc\" and \"Baby Doc\" Duvalier?", "answer": "Haiti", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133af76", "question": "What were American patriots protesting when they dumped tea into Boston Harbor?", "answer": "Taxation without representation", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c1c1", "question": "What nationality was writer, neurologist and psychiatrist Viktor E. Frankl?", "answer": "Austrian", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c29b", "question": "What does a meteorologist study?", "answer": "Weather, more accurately atmosphere and atmospheric changes", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe4ddff06d333868d34d70c", "question": "What was the family name of Mary Queen of Scots?", "answer": "Stuart", "category": "history"}, {"id": "60062d9ac9d816e292245c35", "question": "Who painted \"The Scream\"?", "answer": "Edvard Munch\u00a0painted \"The Scream.\"  His style is recognized by most critics as leading to the birth of German Expressionism.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c890", "question": "What does the Mohs scale measure?", "answer": "Mineral hardness", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133beb9", "question": "Who founded \"Heiress Records\" in 2004?", "answer": "Paris Hilton", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5952489b736d4be723796b74", "question": "What singer, who went to #1 in 1980 with \"Lookin\u2019 For Love\", published \"Still Lookin\u2019 For Love\", as his autobiography?", "answer": "Johnny Lee", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0d1", "question": "In which film did Kevin Costner make his directorial debut?", "answer": "Dances with Wolves", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c081", "question": "People with a lot of hair are said to suffer from what?", "answer": "Hypertrichosis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "592ead00f83302ff91e46475", "question": "Which European city is regarded as the watch making capital of the world?", "answer": "Geneva", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5c5", "question": "In 1643 Evangalista Torichelli invented the first what?", "answer": "Barometer", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb76", "question": "What two countries co-hosted the FIFA World Cup in men's soccer in 2002?", "answer": "Japan and South Korea", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58ec26898dc25ca9e12ef64c", "question": "How many engines are on a B-52 bomber?", "answer": "Eight", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600781fabd51d85e222ab651", "question": "What is the title of Henri Matisse's famous portrait of his wife?", "answer": "In 1905, just prior to such works being derisively labeled as the creations of Les Fauves, he painted\u00a0\"The Green Stripe\".", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fecd87eec223966ae8f88dd", "question": "Which film's antagonist was nicknamed \"Bruce\" after a Hollywood lawyer?", "answer": "\"Jaws\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394ce", "question": "What TV spy often tried to pass himself off as a salesman for the Pontiac Greeting Card Company?", "answer": "Maxwell Smart", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c3c1", "question": "How many horns does the average African black rhino have?", "answer": "Two", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea824fff048f679a45ac20", "question": "What color is second from the top in a rainbow?", "answer": "Orange", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c5b9", "question": "Where are the pig's sweat glands?", "answer": "They don't have any", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa23", "question": "Which country has Budapest as its capital?", "answer": "Hungary", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a8f1", "question": "What harbor is overlooked by Victoria Peak?", "answer": "Hong Kong", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133953c", "question": "What soap opera was on air from 1952 until 2009?", "answer": "Guiding Light", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c82e", "question": "What plant's roots are used to make tapioca?", "answer": "The cassava's", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398e5", "question": "What popular Motown group was originally known as \"The Primettes\"?", "answer": "The Supremes", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dbd", "question": "What Thomas Hardy novel takes its quiet title from Thomas Gray's \"Elegy Written in a Country Churchyard\"?", "answer": "Far from the Madding Crowd", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339f9e", "question": "What kind of bird is Wallace and Gromit's nemesis, Feathers McGraw?", "answer": "A penguin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a360", "question": "What city dug the first subway?", "answer": "London", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe8ff3101dd7bf43be5e861", "question": "Who said, \"I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have.\"?", "answer": "Thomas Jefferson", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b1e2", "question": "Which US president lived in Rancho del Cielo?", "answer": "Ronald Reagan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d8d", "question": "What original literary work was the movie \"Gettysburg\" based on?", "answer": "The Killer Angels", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fcc", "question": "Which writer coined the word \"Cyberspace\"?", "answer": "William Gibson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fd823bfd0de9af39e9d46b2", "question": "What university was Dwight D. Eisenhower president of?", "answer": "Columbia", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c37c", "question": "Who developed the classification we use for clouds?", "answer": "Luke Howard", "category": "science"}, {"id": "597cdd80e347d002c297e4f1", "question": "What tunnel connects France and Italy?", "answer": "Mont Blanc Tunnel", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fecd41bec223966ae8f88ca", "question": "Some of the musical compositions for \"The Hateful Eight\" are unused scores from what movie?", "answer": "\"The Thing\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339c33", "question": "Which actor played the main protagonist in the TV show \"Twin Peaks\"?", "answer": "Kyle MacLachlan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393a8", "question": "In the movie \"Rebel Without A Cause\", who dies in the chicky race?", "answer": "Buzz", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe9f5bbff048f679a45aad8", "question": "An earthquake that measures 8 on the Richter Scale would be how many times stronger than one that measures 4 on the same scale?", "answer": "10,000 times stronger", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339afe", "question": "What 1995 Kevin Costner film was the most expensive movie ever made, until \"Titanic\" came along in 1997?", "answer": "Waterworld", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5febba487e83c707845b2144", "question": "The Philadelphia Flyers of the 1970's were known as the \"Broad Street\" what?", "answer": "Bullies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4d9b3908b8581f80b092c3", "question": "What three gaming consoles did Nintendo release in 2017?", "answer": "Nintendo Switch, New Nintendo 2DS XL, and Super NES Classic Edition", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ba44", "question": "The philanthropist, Andrew Carnegie, made his fortune in what industry?", "answer": "Steel", "category": "general"}, {"id": "58bb3542e368446ca7bd6850", "question": "Which popular method of brewing coffee requires the beans to be ground to a powder?", "answer": "Turkish", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bc2e", "question": "What year did Barbie doll first appear on the market?", "answer": "1959", "category": "general"}, {"id": "601de9f76b1208747aa7e9d5", "question": "In the Chinese zodiac, with which of the five elements is the snake associated?", "answer": "Fire -- It points to aggression and dominance.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b44c", "question": "In 1994, which Scandinavian country voted to stay out of the European Union?", "answer": "Norway", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe65934ae7e414034b5aefc", "question": "What killer was known as the \"Vampire of Dusseldorf\"?", "answer": "Peter Kurten", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338cea", "question": "Who wrote \"The Scarlett Letter\"?", "answer": "Nathaniel Hawthorne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133950d", "question": "How many planets align during the eclipse in the movie \"Lara Croft: Tomb Raider\"", "answer": "Nine", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ff66ce552a821ff76ae8b15", "question": "When and where were the first commercial Christmas cards sold?", "answer": "The first commercial Christmas cards were sold in London in 1843.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133bb49", "question": "What is the telephone area code for the White House?", "answer": "202", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b576", "question": "What is Sauerkraut?", "answer": "Pickled Cabbage", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391ac", "question": "What is Homer Simpson's middle initial?", "answer": "J", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6015dde0fe83fe1f2a824b66", "question": "Where does the color sepia come from?", "answer": "The ink of cuttlefish", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b7f7", "question": "What sauce is used in traditional eggs Benedict?", "answer": "Hollandaise", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113398f2", "question": "How many episodes of \u201cMagnum P.I.\u201d were made?", "answer": "162", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113394c8", "question": "Who owned the detective agency in the TV show \"Remington Steele\"?", "answer": "Laura Holt", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e24", "question": "What kind of dinosaur is the Flintstones' Dino?", "answer": "A snorkasaurus", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fecd1e4ec223966ae8f88c1", "question": "While filming \"Guardians of the Galaxy\", what did director James Gunn give out as rewards to his actors and crew?", "answer": "Play-Doh", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "6014c781fbde8045e48466c3", "question": "What was the first masculine name given to a hurricane?", "answer": "Bob", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fd6656ca5bfecdd737e085f", "question": "What three vows do Catholic priests take?", "answer": "Poverty, chastity and obedience", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339fc9", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional band \"Drive Shaft\"?", "answer": "Lost", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "59523ec4736d4be723796b53", "question": "What three provinces requested a single Dominion be formed in 1867, thus beginning to shape modern Canada?", "answer": "New Brunswick, Nova Scotia and the Province of Canada", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58ab15e4baab681b0929217f", "question": "What was the world\u2019s first mass-produced car to feature an all-aluminium body?", "answer": "Honda NSX", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a0f9", "question": "In the movie \"Stand By Me\", what did Gordy, Chris, Vern and Teddy set out to find?", "answer": "A Body", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133ae37", "question": "What international award did President Theodore Roosevelt win in 1906?", "answer": "Nobel Peace Prize", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59523cf2736d4be723796b3c", "question": "What is Canada\u2019s $1 coin commonly referred to as?", "answer": "Loonie", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5937ee3208d98002fdd633d2", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the Dutch word \"brandewijn\"?", "answer": "Burned wine", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5c3e9b06ebfabb9c85d8a981", "question": "\"Four legs good, two legs bad\" is a quotation from which novel?", "answer": "Animal Farm", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c231", "question": "What animal is on the cover of the Beach Boys' album \"Pet Sounds\"?", "answer": "Goat", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a591", "question": "Which US state is called the Magnolia State?", "answer": "Mississippi", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe0da86fcbed638185eaa05", "question": "Where can you find the world\u2019s smallest penguin?", "answer": "Tasmania", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe8f8f701dd7bf43be5e84a", "question": "What man did Billy Jean King beat in the so-called \"Battle of the Sexes\"", "answer": "Bobby Riggs", "category": "general"}, {"id": "6015ddd1fe83fe1f2a824b64", "question": "Who invented the color wheel?", "answer": "Sir Isaac Newton", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4f7", "question": "What is better than stone in the paper, stone, scissors game?", "answer": "Paper", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff51a0aff04d658268c9304", "question": "Which American revolutionary figure was a philosopher?", "answer": "Thomas Paine, the patriot who penned the philosophical treatise \"The Rights of Man\" and the revolutionary pamphlet \"Common Sense\"", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a6c7", "question": "The resort city of Aspen is located in which US state?", "answer": "Colorado", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a14", "question": "Where does Spanish rain fall, according to \"My Fair Lady\"?", "answer": "On the plain", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339aa5", "question": "What was the nickname of the Spice Girls singer Geri Halliwell?", "answer": "Ginger Spice", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339219", "question": "What actor is known as \"The Fonz\"?", "answer": "Henry Winkler", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fef95ab6ce05a3942286e99", "question": "What was Buzz Lightyear's original name?", "answer": "Lunar Larry", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ab1b3234fda37788a9a1dc0", "question": "What is the basis for guacamole?", "answer": "Avocado", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c38a", "question": "What ferrous alloy has a minimum of 10 percent chromium content?", "answer": "Stainless steel", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338e6d", "question": "Who painted \"Irises\"?", "answer": "Vincent van Gogh", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9e1", "question": "Which Central American country extends furthest north?", "answer": "Belize", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c2e0", "question": "How many honeybees does it take to make one teaspoon of honey?", "answer": "12", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b5e5", "question": "Who founded eBay in 1995?", "answer": "Pierre Omidyar", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a43", "question": "What Bob Marley song did Eric Clapton cover for a #1 hit?", "answer": "I Shot the Sheriff", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c9b5", "question": "What is the name of Stephen Hawking's cosmology book published in 1988?", "answer": "A Brief History of Time", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe6a07020565ad31a57c795", "question": "Which US politician won the presidency on their birthday?", "answer": "Warren Harding", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa87", "question": "Muscat is the capital of which country?", "answer": "Oman", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133ae5d", "question": "What 1980\u2019s US president survived an assassination attempt?", "answer": "Ronald Regan", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339776", "question": "What company did Robert Downey Jr. inherit from his father in Ironman?", "answer": "Stark Industries", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a4d4", "question": "In what US state would you find Area 51?", "answer": "Nevada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fe7730beec85e375820b304", "question": "Where can you find the world's largest naturally frozen ice rink?", "answer": "Canada", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338d38", "question": "What popular comic book character's nickname is \"Man of Steel\"?", "answer": "Superman", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "597cd9dae347d002c297e4d0", "question": "What became the tallest building in London after its official opening in October 1965?", "answer": "Post Office Tower", "category": "history"}, {"id": "59f47342cfb6472aeed499d5", "question": "What is a \"Papoose\"?", "answer": "A Native American Child", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff51aafff04d658268c9308", "question": "Who was Telemachus?", "answer": "Telemachus was the only son of Odysseus and Penelope.", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133998b", "question": "What was the name of the main police detective played by Jack Webb on the TV show \"Dragnet\"?", "answer": "Joe Friday", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339af9", "question": "The bands Whitesnake and Rainbow were both splinter groups from what British rock band?", "answer": "Deep Purple", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133a05f", "question": "With which singer did Westlife record a version of \"Against all Odds\" in 2000?", "answer": "Mariah Carey", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5b3234debf195a31e15d73a9", "question": "Who played Derek Flint in the 1966 film \"Our Man Flint\"?", "answer": "James Coburn", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133ca86", "question": "What culinary ingredient did Hippolyte M\u00e8ge-Mouri\u00e8s invent?", "answer": "Margarine", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339336", "question": "What was the title of the TV series \"M*A*S*H\" theme song?", "answer": "Suicide is Painless", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113395ca", "question": "In The Simpsons, what is the name of Kirk Van Houten's demo singing tape?", "answer": "Can I Borrow a Feeling?", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe8b30d01dd7bf43be5e7a7", "question": "What US state is home to the Crazy Horse Memorial?", "answer": "South Dakota", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5f164c83f9b80650dbe7f92f", "question": "Who plays Thor in the 2017 film \"Thor: Ragnarok\"?", "answer": "Chris Hemsworth", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5963702f967692ea851899b8", "question": "What singer scored a #1 hit in 1999 with a duet with his wife, Lisa Hartman entitled, \"When I Said I Do\"?", "answer": "Clint Black", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a7b2", "question": "In what city is Purdue University located?", "answer": "West Lafayette, IN", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5ff25a8431a458464a93c472", "question": "Which condiment is traditionally served with fried seafood in the United States?", "answer": "Tartar Sauce", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339d2c", "question": "What sport is the focus of the movie \"Fat City\"?", "answer": "Boxing", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338a80", "question": "Who wrote the novel Oryx and Crake?", "answer": "Margaret Atwood", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390a1", "question": "What is Demeter the god of?", "answer": "Harvest and agriculture", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe69aab20565ad31a57c756", "question": "In the Bible, who is the wife of Boaz?", "answer": "Ruth", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fa7", "question": "Who painted \"The 3rd of May\"?", "answer": "Francisco de Goya", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bb98", "question": "What athletic apparel company took its name from the Greek goddess of Victory?", "answer": "Nike", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c41b", "question": "What is the common word for a weight suspended from a pivot that can move freely?", "answer": "A pendulum", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59f9b9cb364247bf200fb891", "question": "Who is credited with designing the icon look of the Morris Mini-Minor?", "answer": "Alec Issigonis", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113391a4", "question": "What city is the TV show \"Sex and the City\" based in?", "answer": "New York", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5ffa38e9c73aa70ea0b70ad6", "question": "How many U.S. states are named after a President?", "answer": "One (Washington is named after George Washington, the first U.S. president.)", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd821ffd0de9af39e9d46a7", "question": "What was the first species of animal sent to space?", "answer": "Fruit Fly", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fea489bff048f679a45abb1", "question": "If you throw a ball in the air, what curve does it trace out?", "answer": "Parabola", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c283", "question": "How often are brain cells replaced?", "answer": "Never", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113390e0", "question": "Which English playwright wrote the play \"The Alchemist\"?", "answer": "Ben Jonson", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c031", "question": "What is the fear of fire known as?", "answer": "Pyrophobia", "category": "general"}, {"id": "600f721aa9e54d890926f6ea", "question": "In which ocean can you find Australia\u2019s Great Barrier Reef?", "answer": "Pacific -- It is comprised of over 3,000 reef systems and contains over 400 different types of coral and is visible from space.", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3fc", "question": "Who was James Garfield's vice president?", "answer": "Chester A. Arthur", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe6a56220565ad31a57c7cb", "question": "Which US President owned a haberdashery?", "answer": "Harry S. Truman", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ede129f031133c86e", "question": "What fruit is a hybrid of the mandarin orange and the grapefruit?", "answer": "The tangelo", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fe8f49001dd7bf43be5e823", "question": "What is America's oldest brewery?", "answer": "Yuengling", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c819", "question": "In what part of the body would you find amniotic fluid?", "answer": "The uterus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c7c0", "question": "What did Pieter van Musschenbroek create at a namesake Dutch university in 1746 by lining a glass jar with silver foil?", "answer": "The Leyden jar", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5fea40e6ff048f679a45ab6b", "question": "What does the substance melanin control?", "answer": "Color of skin", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bcf", "question": "In Norse mythology who are the female attendants of Odin?", "answer": "The Valkyrie", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "6015f7c9fe83fe1f2a824c26", "question": "Who was the UK\u2019s second woman Prime Minister?", "answer": "Theresa May", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdc7", "question": "What is the primary ingredient in the silvery amalgam used in dental restoration?", "answer": "Mercury", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133aa83", "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Colorado?", "answer": "Denver", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b655", "question": "The entrance to what New York City landmark has a pair of lion sculptures?", "answer": "Public Library", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338fdb", "question": "Who was the Roman goddess of Peace?", "answer": "Pax", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bff4", "question": "Guru Nanak founded which religion?", "answer": "Sikhism", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b105", "question": "In 1935, what American celebrity, tired of years of hounding by the press, moved his entire family to England?", "answer": "Charles Lindbergh", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396b5", "question": "What movie features the line: \"You can't handle the truth\"?", "answer": "A Few Good Men", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe767f8eec85e375820b29c", "question": "Which city is considered the birthplace of democracy?", "answer": "Athens, Greece", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5fd18b1329d03ab85b632b2e", "question": "Who said, \"Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity, and I'm not sure about the universe\"?", "answer": "Einstein", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef5f566ce05a3942286e41", "question": "Who was the highest paid athlete of 2018?", "answer": "Floyd Mayweather", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338dd0", "question": "From what language did English borrow the word \"glitch\"?", "answer": "Yiddish", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe9f24eff048f679a45aab8", "question": "What type of cloud is often described as \"cotton-like\"?", "answer": "Cumulus", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338b7a", "question": "What novel won John Steinbeck a Pulitzer Prize in 1940?", "answer": "Grapes of Wrath", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5a9e96b07ccba3ffe45786f0", "question": "What area in the US translates from the Dutch as \"Marshland\"?", "answer": "Brooklyn", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133be39", "question": "How many players are there in a standard team handball team?", "answer": "Seven", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bd3e", "question": "What holiday is celebrated with an aluminum pole, the Airing of Grievances, and Feats of Strength?", "answer": "Festivus", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b6", "question": "Who did Abraham Lincoln face in a series of debates in 1858?", "answer": "Stephen Douglas", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f031133991d", "question": "In \"Legally Blonde\", what magazine does Elle Woods refer to as \"the Bible\"?", "answer": "Cosmopolitan", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5a4a975661d1b4d384d5d683", "question": "Where would you find a \"crossbuck\"?", "answer": "At a railroad crossing", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b8de", "question": "In which hand is the Statue of Liberty holding a torch?", "answer": "Right hand", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5906837bff9c0647b50a80a7", "question": "Which electronic duo did The Weeknd collaborate with for his song, \"Starboy\"?", "answer": "Daft Punk", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c03b", "question": "How many stars are on the flag of New Zealand?", "answer": "Four", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5b6990cae762b54eb9be9414", "question": "How old was Janet Leigh in her debut film \"The Romance of Rosy Ridge\"?", "answer": "20", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b285", "question": "What position was first held by Steve Allen?", "answer": "Tonight Show host", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b604", "question": "What war do the girls in \"Little Women\" grow up during?", "answer": "The Civil War", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fef5bab6ce05a3942286e18", "question": "What was the name of Bob Ross' TV show?", "answer": "\"The Joy of Painting\"", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5bde129f031133a9bb", "question": "Approximately, how many times larger than Rhode Island is Texas?", "answer": "257", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5cefc09b948005ec986edcdd", "question": "Who is the fourth member of the group LOONA to debut?", "answer": "Yeojin", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0b3", "question": "In what year did the Chicago Black Hawks win their first Stanley Cup?", "answer": "1934", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe93c216bd93ce3a4e5f6aa", "question": "The bark of which tree is fireproof?", "answer": "Redwoods", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113389af", "question": "Whose wife was turned into a pillar of salt?", "answer": "Lot's", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "60078c190eee65b76b9f266f", "question": "America stayed neutral in World War I until Germany threatened what?", "answer": "Commercial shipping (In March 1917, four U.S. commercial ships were sunk by Germany, and the U.S. declared war in April 1917.)", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b95d", "question": "What is the first prime number that comes after 100?", "answer": "101", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339b50", "question": "What was the name of Derek Zoolander's rival male model, played by Owen Wilson, in the 2001 movie \"Zoolander\"?", "answer": "Hansel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339a00", "question": "What 1981 thriller opens with the discovery of three faceless corpses at an amusement park in Russia?", "answer": "Gorky Park", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b2d6", "question": "What military legend was nicknamed \"The Marble Man\"?", "answer": "Robert E. Lee", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113397eb", "question": "Which famous duo also recorded under the name \"Tom and Jerry\"?", "answer": "Simon and Garfunkel", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338bb3", "question": "How many symphonies did Beethoven compose?", "answer": "9", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd58de129f03113388d5", "question": "Which series of novels refer to its main character as \"The Last Gunslinger\"?", "answer": "The Dark Tower", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c840", "question": "In what organ of the human body would you find the islets of Langerhans?", "answer": "The pancreas", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b867", "question": "In which sport do you \"shag\" flies?", "answer": "Baseball", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311339164", "question": "Who directed \"Raiders of the Lost Ark\"?", "answer": "Steven Spielberg", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fea7e7fff048f679a45ac10", "question": "Belonephobia is the fear of what?", "answer": "Pins and needles?", "category": "science"}, {"id": "59008be9cf842fa4c4ba969b", "question": "The Gobi Desert lies within which two countries?", "answer": "China and Mongolia", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113396dc", "question": "What alien comes from the planet Melmac?", "answer": "Alf", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5fe4b7df06d333868d34d6fb", "question": "What African state fought a 31-year war for independence from Ethiopia?", "answer": "Eritrea", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5fe4b31d06d333868d34d6d6", "question": "According to the Bible, who was the first King of Israel?", "answer": "Saul", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bed9", "question": "In golf what would you put in your shag bag?", "answer": "Practice balls", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5ff51862ff04d658268c92ff", "question": "What is the most number of years a U.S. president can serve?", "answer": "Ten years -- two years from a previous president's election plus two four-year terms. This is based on the 22nd Amendment.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339cb6", "question": "What TV show featured the fictional \"The Caribou Lodge\" fraternity?", "answer": "Everybody Loves Raymond", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f03113393bd", "question": "What actor played Hunter S. Thompson in the movie \"Where The Buffalo Roam\"?", "answer": "Bill Murray", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "58f566fa33a95c66dc4fe767", "question": "Who directed the 1941 film \"Citizen Kane\"?", "answer": "Orson Welles", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b0d6", "question": "Who was called \"The Hero of San Juan Hill\"?", "answer": "Theodore Roosevelt", "category": "history"}, {"id": "601b4c0e49076251badbeacc", "question": "Who got married in the very first White House wedding?", "answer": "Dolley Madison\u2019s sister -- Lucy Payne Washington, the sister of First Lady Dolley Madison, married Thomas Todd in 1819.", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5e8a66949a45431f553a9ccf", "question": "Who is the original presenter and Taskmaster on the UK television show \"Taskmaster\"?", "answer": "Greg Davies", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b4dc", "question": "What two alcoholic ingredients is the traditional Martini cocktail made of?", "answer": "Gin and vermouth", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133c39e", "question": "What bird bone is known as the \"wishbone\"?", "answer": "Collarbone", "category": "science"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b043", "question": "Which US first lady had several half-\u00adbrothers who served in the Confederate Army?", "answer": "Mary Todd Lincoln", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b29d", "question": "What US president loved Fresca so much he had a soda tap installed for the Oval Office?", "answer": "Lyndon Johnson", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339e8f", "question": "What William Boyd character headlined TV's first western?", "answer": "Hopalong Cassidy", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338c9c", "question": "Who wrote \"Around the World in Eighty Days\"?", "answer": "Jules Verne", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5fe255d1658e585fda9cfa34", "question": "What was the original name of Diet Pepsi?", "answer": "Patio Diet Cola", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f0311339bb2", "question": "What band's 1993 debut album was entitled \"August and Everything After\"?", "answer": "Counting Crows", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5906818bff9c0647b50a8094", "question": "Which Gabor sister, who passed away in December of 2016, was crowned Miss Hungary in 1936?", "answer": "Zsa Zsa Gabor", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b49e", "question": "Which country hosted the first Olympic Games after World War I?", "answer": "Belgium", "category": "history"}, {"id": "5867fd59de129f0311338efb", "question": "Which literary work's title character is named Michael Henchard?", "answer": "The Mayor of Casterbridge", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5ff6673052a821ff76ae8afc", "question": "How much did Judas Iscariot receive for betraying Jesus Christ?", "answer": "\"30 pieces of silver\"", "category": "arts"}, {"id": "5867fd5ade129f03113399b6", "question": "The band Duran Duran took its name from a character in what Jane Fonda sci-fi movie?", "answer": "Barbarella", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5cde129f031133b3cc", "question": "Who invented the Gatling gun?", "answer": "Richard Jordan Gatling", "category": "history"}, {"id": "58d06c40870e6f05ba600852", "question": "What character did Drew Barrymore play in the 1995 film \"Boys on the Side\"?", "answer": "Holly Pulchik", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bf58", "question": "What do the letters A and W stand for in the \"A&W\" root beer name?", "answer": "Allen and Wright", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5fedddea6ce05a3942286da8", "question": "Which actress claims she cried when she was shown her wardrobe for the role of the monarch in the 2006 film \"The Queen\"?", "answer": "Helen Mirren", "category": "entertainment"}, {"id": "5867fd5dde129f031133bdbe", "question": "What is traditionally the main fruit ingredient in a rickey?", "answer": "Limes", "category": "general"}, {"id": "5990f4affa5fdd6dd25324e3", "question": "Bangui is the capital of which land-locked African country?", "answer": "Central African Republic", "category": "geography"}, {"id": "6010ca8b0775fa611bce67fa", "question": "For what category is the Charlemagne Prize awarded?", "answer": "Work toward European unification -- Awarded to projects run by persons aged 16 to 30 that promote the idea of a unified Europe.", "category": "general"}]